{
    "subject": "resource/WLGZ-FM",
    "predicate": "property/city",
    "object": "resource/Webster,_New_York",
    "human_readable": "WLGZ-FM is based in Webster, New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8987770676612854,
            "question": "Where is WLGZ-FM based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7368059754371643,
            "question": "Is there a history of radio broadcasting in Webster, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6662597060203552,
            "question": "What state is Webster, New York in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6647194623947144,
            "question": "Who owns or operates WLGZ-FM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6468143463134766,
            "question": "Is WLGZ-FM a radio station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5492579340934753,
            "question": "Are there any other media outlets in Webster, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4736194312572479,
            "question": "What is the call sign for WLGZ-FM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4236864149570465,
            "question": "Does WLGZ-FM have a website or social media presence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37703433632850647,
            "question": "What is the population of Webster, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3022027611732483,
            "question": "What kind of programming does WLGZ-FM likely offer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WLGZ-FM is based in Webster, New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6240_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the population of Webster, New York?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6240_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does WLGZ-FM have a website or social media presence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6240_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the call sign for WLGZ-FM?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6240_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6240_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the radio station WLGZ-FM being located in Webster, New York. Specifically, several documents state that it is licensed to and serves this area, confirming the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}